Brenda Fini

PROFILE

Creative, certified maintenance professional with close to a decade of experience. Trained in electrical maintenance but capable of working in HVACR in a team-based or independent capacity. A leader with project management experience and a strong work ethic.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

General Maintenance Worker

Tobbian Maintenance Corp., Decatur, IL | February 2014-Present

- Perform basic HVACR repair for commercial and residential buildings
- Assist maintenance supervisor in repurposing old equipment, saving the company 7% per month in expenses
- Maintain service and repair records for regulatory compliance
- Worked with team to ensure buildings passed necessary inspections
- Acting lead when the supervisor was out of the office

Junior Maintenance Technician

Lincoln Land Community College, Springfield, IL | November 2011-January 2014

- Provided general building maintenance and repair
- Maintained parts and supplies inventory
- Assisted senior maintenance technicians during new equipment installation
- Read and used electrical drawings

EDUCATION

Associate in Applied Science (AAS) in Commercial Electrical Maintenance

Lincoln Land Community College, Springfield, IL June 2010-May 2012

KEY SKILLS

- HVACR and electric maintenance
- Reading blueprints and schematics
- Time management and organization skills
- Preventative and reparative maintenance
- Project management and effective communication

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Maintenance Technician I (CMT-I)
- Certified Maintenance & Reliability Technician (CMRT)
- Certificate in HVACR